So, HEX has actually been on a nice run.
Um we had a nice move off of these lows.
You know, I told you guys this is
actually kind of insane a couple days
ago, like right before this pump, I told
you guys the ecosystem was ready and we
had a huge run up on pretty much
everything. HEX has pumped as high as
173%
off of this recent move. And we had some
dips,
but we had a really nice recovery. So,
this is actually looking It's not
looking great, but that was a good move.
I want to see Yesterday I was saying I
want to see a We'll call it, you know,
1,000 or 10,000 hold, but we've broken
that. We're under it. You know, there's
nothing
concerning. This is a natural nice
natural move.
I would start to get concerned if we
just have constant red candles. If we
have a red candle today and then another
red candle tomorrow and another one the
next day,
it's it's just not going to be looking
good. It's It's All of my confidence
will be drained. So, what I want to see
is I want to see bullish activities. I
want to see this candle right here just
snap right back up, get back above
1,000. If we get back above 1,000,
I'm going to be feeling pretty
[clears throat] bullish. Same thing
yesterday
or the day before whenever that was.
We had a dump and I said, "Well, is that
it?" And the buyers [clears throat]
stepped right back in, started running
it back up, running it back up 2 days
straight, and now we're having another
pullback. Now, who is buying HEX? I
actually think that this is Richard
Heart buying. Before we get into that,
got some updates for you guys. So, if
you're not familiar, I am the founder of
mortokens.com. I created a HEX-type
staking platform where there is no
inflation. It has a cap supply and the
yield is paid by penalties for people
who unstake early and unstake late. So,
instead of the you having penalties from
early unstakers, late unstakers, and
inflation, just we just took the
inflation part of it out. So,
um it's working
flawlessly. So, I seen this
um this morning and I said, "Man, this
guy staked 585 more for 212 days
and he held it for 332 days and he still
made 17%." And I started to panic cuz
I'm like, "Oh my god, there's a flaw in
the contract because he's supposed to be
in the red here. He's supposed to This
is a extra 120 days that he was late.
So, he should be in the red." So, I
said, "You know what? Let's put another
column that shows how much penalties
were paid." So, let's hit refresh. And
now you can see the penalty. So, they
staked 500, they unstaked 585, and they
paid 104 in penalties, and they still
So, they still made a small ROI, which
is pretty cool. So, yeah, check out
mortokens.com. I would say, I mean, I
know it's me, but I would say don't
sleep on it, man. Don't fade it. It's
it's it's fun. Like, it's working as
intended. I had was kind of concerned
cuz I'm like, "Man, everybody's going to
don't nobody's going to stake on time
and end early and and there's not going
to be any fees." But, it's beautiful how
it's working. So, it's on PulseChain,
it's on Ethereum, it's on Avalanche. And
look out for Fuel. If you want to read
about Fuel, check the white paper.
Uh all right, let's get back to HEX.
Now,
who is buying HEX? I actually think that
this is Richard Heart buying.
I don't think that this is just
"Oh, I'm going to buy some HEX. People
are starting to buy HEX." I don't think
so. I think this is Richard Heart
deploying and testing and seeing if the
price is ready to go. Because what's
happening is I don't I'm not going to do
it right now because I don't I don't
really feel like it, but
I was watching
we'll call it the order book, right? And
you'll see these big sales. Like I saw
like a 6,000 $6,000 worth of HEX on this
day right here, one of these days.
And I said, "Wow." And then you just
start seeing and it starts coming in
like a buying burst. $30, $20, it starts
buying up.
So, what I think is happening is
I'm not sure, but I
can imagine this [clears throat] is
what's happening is
Richard Heart has on some bots.
And we saw when we saw that test pump,
I'm not sure when that was on on Pulse,
but I think that was the bots being
turned on.
And I
honestly think that he has a wallet
or set of wallets with a ton of funds in
them
and they're just tick buying
the token. They're just buying buying
cuz what happens is
you get a sell-off and then you get one
person to sell. There's not many people
in HEX and PulseChain who have still
have liquid HEX. Can you imagine having
liquid HEX right now? Like
it's dust basically.
No matter how much HEX you have, it's
dust relative to how much
it was. So, if you're selling
any amount, it's not a lot anymore.
So,
and and those people are few and far
between.
So,
I'm thinking that the bots are on
and the point that it stops going up is
the point where my stakes start to get
heavy again. Like any HEX that I have
staked, I'm not selling my principal.
I think and I think that's how most
Hexicans move and operate if they've
been in it for a long time. So, someone
like me who was in from the beginning,
like this is your sock. You're listening
to somebody who's friend it from the
beginning, who's actually still playing
the game, who's still actually staking,
re-staking, has done the whole thing,
right? I take my interest, I sell that,
and then I re-stake for and I max stake
because I have a whole ladder. So, it's
like I might as well just do it for the
max stake at this point. Everything
Everything every new stake or every
stake that I end, I max stake it.
So, and it's at what point do I stop
doing that? Because I learned my lesson.
My lesson was no you may be emergency in
stake.
Then come back later. See, I know I got
that new information. So, I'm not going
to do the same
or we are not going to do the same thing
that we were going to do that we did
last time.
We're going to learn from that. So, at
what point do I start to say, "Okay, I'm
taking I'm selling this some of this
principal."
And I don't it's not around here. Not at
these prices. I'm still just going to
sell my my interest.
So, we'll see. It's still a little bit
too early to tell. This is a very
critical day though because we have an
engulfing candle. So, we're eating this
candle right here.
So,
um
if we close like this,
it's going to start looking a little
choppy. But,
it still could just chop and hold 73.
I would say as long as we don't go below
and stay, it's pretty bullish. If we get
to 73 like we did back here and we
bounce, it could still continue to be a
bullish but a bullish move. But, it
would need to bounce and get all the way
back up to, you know, 95. We got to keep
stay around this
um this 1,000 range.
If we go down here, we got to get back
up immediately. We can't do things like
this. We can't dip and then not bounce.
Just if you look at look at the down
moves on we pumped.
Pumped and then just wicks right back
down. Pump and it's right back down.
Pump and it's right back down.
And you could say we're something doing
something like this.
But,
we did this the other day, but the price
went right back up, see?
This was trying to be one of these.
But,
it got eight right back up. So, some
This is very bullish. The fact that we
did this.
Um
yeah, that's where I'm at with it for
HEX.